{
	"level1": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "Boss 2 * 3 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"2",
				"5",
				"6"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "Boss 4 / 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"24",
				"2",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 5",
			"options": [
				"55",
				"10",
				"25",
				"52"
			],
			"answer": "25"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "Boss 3 * 4",
			"options": [
				"7",
				"12",
				"4",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "12"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "Boss 1 * 1",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"2",
				"3",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "1"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 3",
			"options": [
				"45",
				"35",
				"53",
				"15"
			],
			"answer": "15"
		}
	},
	"level2": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "Boss 2 * 3 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"2",
				"5",
				"6"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "Boss 4 / 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"24",
				"2",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 5",
			"options": [
				"55",
				"10",
				"25",
				"52"
			],
			"answer": "25"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "Boss 3 * 4",
			"options": [
				"7",
				"12",
				"4",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "12"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "Boss 1 * 1",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"2",
				"3",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "1"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 3",
			"options": [
				"45",
				"35",
				"53",
				"15"
			],
			"answer": "15"
		}
	},
	"level3": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "Boss 2 * 3 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"2",
				"5",
				"6"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "Boss 4 / 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"24",
				"2",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 5 = ?",
			"options": [
				"55",
				"10",
				"25",
				"52"
			],
			"answer": "25"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "Boss 3 * 4 = ?",
			"options": [
				"7",
				"12",
				"4",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "12"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "Boss 1 * 1",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"2",
				"3",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "1"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 3",
			"options": [
				"45",
				"35",
				"53",
				"15"
			],
			"answer": "15"
		}
	},
	"level4": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "Boss 2 * 3 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"2",
				"5",
				"6"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "Boss 4 / 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"24",
				"2",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 5",
			"options": [
				"55",
				"10",
				"25",
				"52"
			],
			"answer": "25"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "Boss 3 * 4",
			"options": [
				"7",
				"12",
				"4",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "12"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "Boss 1 * 1",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"2",
				"3",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "1"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 3",
			"options": [
				"45",
				"35",
				"53",
				"15"
			],
			"answer": "15"
		}
	},
	"level5": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "Boss 2 * 3 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"2",
				"5",
				"6"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "Boss 4 / 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"24",
				"2",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 5",
			"options": [
				"55",
				"10",
				"25",
				"52"
			],
			"answer": "25"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "Boss 3 * 4",
			"options": [
				"7",
				"12",
				"4",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "12"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "Boss 1 * 1",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"2",
				"3",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "1"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 3",
			"options": [
				"45",
				"35",
				"53",
				"15"
			],
			"answer": "15"
		}
	},
	"level6": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "Boss 2 * 3 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"2",
				"5",
				"6"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "Boss 4 / 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"3",
				"24",
				"2",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 5",
			"options": [
				"55",
				"10",
				"25",
				"52"
			],
			"answer": "25"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "Boss 3 * 4",
			"options": [
				"7",
				"12",
				"4",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "12"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "Boss 1 * 1",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"2",
				"3",
				"4"
			],
			"answer": "1"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "Boss 5 * 3",
			"options": [
				"45",
				"35",
				"53",
				"15"
			],
			"answer": "15"
		}
	}
}